What is the worth of this
dunya
If you compare it to akhirah
Accept us
Any one of you
Will insert his finger
Inside the ocean
Let him see what is it that
That finger will bring out
from water
The comparison, the
illustration of the vast
difference
Between the joy
Between the comfort
Between the luxury of this
dunya
And the joy and the luxury of
the goodness
And all of these of akhirah
Is that place one finger into
the
water
To the ocean
Atlantic, Pacific
Place one finger into it
Remove the finger
Can you compare the quantity
of water
on your hands
To the quantity of water in
the
ocean
That is the similarity
That is how small this dunya
is